http://www.rosesw.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Welcoming to Rosesw. We respect and try to protect the privacy of our visitors and customers. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy.
1 Registration and Ordering:During registration, you will be prompted to provide us with your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address and credit card number.
In addition, we may also ask you for your country so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and we might also ask for your gender. These types of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes.
If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide us with to contact you.
2 We have McAfee and Norton Internet Security to process securely online credit card transaction.
Your payment detail is encrypted and cannot be read as it travels over the internet.
3 Privacy Security: Third Parties
We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business. The details you provide to us will not be sold to third party organizations; they may only be shared for the purpose of processing your chosen order as outlined above.
We use the latest encryption technology, and all employees that we hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access.
